Guide to the Gay & Lesbian Advocates & Defenders Records
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- Additional material, 1975-1999; Accession 2015-M-014
  - Parameters for The Transportation Program, 1995 October (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Documents produced by Bragdon -originals, 1-13, 1995 May (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Documents produced by Bragdon -originals, 14-47, 1995 May (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Documents produced by Donald Craven - originals, 1-11, Undated (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Documents produced by Donald Craven - originals, 12-18, Undated (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Documents produced by Sanford Kuvin - originals, 1987, undated (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Sanford F. Kuvin: Expert witness Curriculum Vitae, Undated (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Cases in which Kuvin testified, 1995 May (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Documents produced by Randon Bragdon, D.M.D., 1-11, Undated (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Documents produced by Randon Bragdon, D.M.D., 12-47, Undated (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Abbott v. Bragdon -Pleadings Binder #1 1-25, 1994-1995 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Abbott v. Bragdon -Pleadings Binder #1 26-50, 1994-1995 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Abbott v. Bragdon -Pleadings Binder #2 1-25, 1995-1996 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Abbott v. Bragdon -Pleadings Binder #2 26-50, 1995-1996 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Abbott v. Bragdon -Pleadings Binder #2, 1995-1996 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Equal Employment Opportunity Commission v. Commercial Office Products Company, 1988 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Opening statement notes, Undated (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Folder containing articles and notes, 1995-1998 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Press Packet on Bragdon v. Abbott, Undated (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Bragdon v. Abbott, 1994 October (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Expert: Bragdon - Deposition exhibits, 1995 May (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Bragdon deposition notes/outlines, Undated (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Infected health care workers materials, 1992 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Health care worker cases, 1995 June (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Legal research: Commerce Clause, Undated (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Legal Research: Fiduciary Duty, Undated (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Deposition of Randon Bragdon, DMD - original, 1994 November (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Affidavit of Donald E. Craven, M.D., 1995 September (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Affidavit of Donald E. Craven, M.D., 1995 September (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Affidavit of John A. Molinari, PH.D, 1995 September (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Affidavit of John A. Molinari, PH.D, 1995 September (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Discrimination in the workplace, 1992-1993 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - O'Conner--Legislative History, 1993 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Souter, David--Legislative history, Circa 1994-1995 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Kennedey--Legislative History, 1988-1993 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Bragdon v. Abbott - research, 1978-1989 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - DOE v. Bragdon - Settlement documents and counsel, 1994-1995 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Legal History -- Supreme court cases, 1989-1997 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Legal History -- Supreme court cases, 1989-1997 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Additional documents produced by Bragdon, 1981-1995 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Sidney Abbott's dental chart, Undated (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Sidney Abbott's registration and health record, Undated (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Fed. deposition exhibits- Letter to Dr. Bragdon from Down East Community Hospital, 1994-1995 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Fed. deposition exhibits- Bragdon v. Abbott interrogatories, 1995 May (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Fed. deposition exhibits- Defendant's response to plaintiff's request for admissions, 1994-1995 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Fed. deposition exhibits- Bragdon v. Abbott answers to plaintiffs first set of Interrog., 1995 May (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Fed. deposition exhibits- Sidney Abbotts appointment, 1994 September (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Fed. deposition exhibits- Bragdon v. Abbott - blank forms, Undated (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Fed. deposition exhibits-Blank dental chart and registration and health chart, Undated (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - Fed. deposition exhibits- Infectious disease policy, 1978 September (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - Fed. deposition exhibits- Def. defenses and ans. To amended complaint and demand for jury trial, 1995 April (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - Fed. deposition exhibits-Def. response to plaintiff's first request for production of documents, 1995 May (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - Fed. deposition exhibits-Bragdon's expert report and documents reviewed, 1995 May (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - Fed. deposition exhibits- Bragdon's yellow pages advertisement, 1995 (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - Legal research: Patient's Assn/intervention, 1995 (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - Legal research: Summary judgment notes, 1995 September (Box 8, Folder 14)
  - Deposition of Randon Bragdon, D.M.D pages 1-183, 1995 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Deposition of Randon Bragdon, D.M.D pages 184-366, 1995 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Plaintiff's submission of deposition testimony in response to issues raised by patient's ……., 1995 (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Documents reviewed by Randon Bragdon Table of contents 1-13, Undated (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - Documents reviewed by Randon Bragdon Table of contents 14-47, Undated (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - Documents produced by Donald Craven Table of contents 1-12, Undated (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - Documents produced by Donald Craven Table of contents 13-17, Undated (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - Documents produced by Donald Craven Table of contents 1-13, Undated (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - Documents produced by Donald Craven Table of contents 12-18, Undated (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - Documents produced by Sanford F. Kuvin Table of contents 1-12, Undated (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - Documents produced by Sanford F. Kuvin Table of contents 13-18, Undated (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - Documents produced by Sanford F. Kuvin, Undated (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - Documents produced by Sanford F. Kuvin, Undated (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - Documents produced by Sanford F. Kuvin, Undated (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - Documents produced by Sanford F. Kuvin, Undated (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - Documents produced by John A. Molinari Table of contents 1-12, Undated (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - Documents produced by John A. Molinari Table of contents 13-19, Undated (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - Bragdon v. Abbott -Handwritten note, Undated (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - Bragdon v. Abbott -Letter, 1999 October (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - Bragdon v. Abbott - Misc., 1994-1999 (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - Bragdon v. Abbott - Misc., 1994-1999 (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - Legal research:-Fundamental alteration, 1995 August (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - Legal research: Expert qualifications, 1995 (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - Misc. materials, 1991 (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - Donor mailings - blank, Undated (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - FRE: Religious objection, 1995 June (Box 13, Folder 9)
  - Deposition of Sanford F. Kuvin, 1995 July (Box 13, Folder 10)
  - Plaintiff's memo in support of motion to exclude expert reports and testimony of Bragdon, 1995 September (Box 13, Folder 11)
  - Correspondence, 1999 (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - Bragdon v. Abbott cases and material for atty. Fees, 1997 July (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - Atty's fees petition--cases and materials, 1996-1997 (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - Abbott: Attorney's fees: Settlement agreement, 1999 September (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - Bragdon v. Abbott - Attorney's fees motion, 1994-1997 (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - Bragdon costs, Undated (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - Bragdon costs documentation, 1995-1997 (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - Expenses, 1995 (Box 14, Folder 8)
  - Sidney Abbott misc. costs, 1995 (Box 14, Folder 9)
  - Bragdon Appellate pleadings Table of contents 1-24, 1996 (Box 14, Folder 10)
  - Bragdon Appellate pleadings Table of contents 25-39, 1996 (Box 14, Folder 11)
  - Bragdon - Discovery documents produced by defendant, 1990-1993 (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - Bragdon - Discovery documents produced by defendant, 1990-1993 (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - Documents produced by Bragdon 1-501, 1991-1994 (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - Documents produced by Bragdon 1-501, 1991-1994 (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - Documents produced by Bragdon 1-501, 1991-1994 (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - Documents produced by Bragdon 502-815, 1991-1994 (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - Documents produced by Bragdon 502-815, 1991-1994 (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - Documents produced by Bragdon 502-815, 1991-1994 (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - Documents produced by Bragdon 502-815, 1991-1994 (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - Documents produced by Bragdon 816-1040, 1993-1997 (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - Documents produced by Bragdon 816-1040, 1993-1994 (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - Documents produced by Bragdon 816-1040, 1993-1994 (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - Documents produced by Bragdon 816-1040, 1993-1994 (Box 17, Folder 4)
  - Costs, 1996-1999 (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - Bragdon costs, 1996-1999 (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - Motion reconsider, Undated (Box 18, Folder 3)
  - Motion notes, Undated (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - Motion notes, Undated (Box 18, Folder 5)
  - Intervention law, Undated (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - Injunctive relief cases, 1975-1978 (Box 18, Folder 7)
  - Injunctive relief cases, 1975-1978 (Box 18, Folder 8)
  - Abbott v. Bragdon - summary judgment, 1995 September (Box 18, Folder 9)
  - Legal research: standing cases, 1995 August (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - Legal research: standing cases, 1994-1995 (Box 19, Folder 2)
  - Legal research: Misc. cases in support of D's summary judgment, Undated (Box 19, Folder 3)
  - Deposition pages cited in defendant's motion for summary judgment, 1995 (Box 19, Folder 4)
  - Misc. papers, 1995 (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - Expert Kuvin: Deposition and admissions for summary judgment, 1995 August (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - Expert Kuvin: Deposition transcript, (Floppy disk in this folder), 1995 July (Box 20, Folder 3)
  - Expert Kuvin: Documents, 1995 September (Box 20, Folder 4)
  - Expert Kuvin: Supplemental documents, 1995 August (Box 20, Folder 5)
  - Expert Kuvin: Supplemental documents, 1995 September (Box 20, Folder 6)
  - Expert Kuvin: BK deposition notes/outlines (CV in this folder), 1995 July (Box 20, Folder 7)
  - Expert Bragdon: Documents 1 of 2 (where is 2?), 1995 September (Box 20, Folder 8)
  - Expert Kuvin: EEOC v. Doe, 1994-1995 (Box 20, Folder 9)
  - Expert Kuvin: EEOC v. Doe Kuvin deposition pages 1-225, 1995 January (Box 20, Folder 10)
  - Expert Kuvin: EEOC v. Doe Kuvin deposition pages 226-416, 1995 January (Box 20, Folder 11)
  - Expert Kuvin: Documents relied upon in expert report, Undated (Box 21, Folder 1)
  - Expert Kuvin: Deposition notes, Undated (Box 21, Folder 2)
  - Expert Kuvin: Deposition exhibits, 1995 July (Box 21, Folder 3)
  - Expert Kuvin: Documents, 1995 (Box 21, Folder 4)
  - Bragdon: Miscellaneous, 1992-1994 (Box 21, Folder 5)
  - Expert Kuvin: Documents handed out at deposition, 1992-1995 (Box 21, Folder 6)
  - Misc. papers, 1991-1994 (Box 21, Folder 7)
  - Expert Kuvin: Curriculum Vitae, Undated (Box 21, Folder 8)
  - Notes: Oral argument, Undated (Box 21, Folder 9)
  - Bragdon (general)??, Undated (Box 21, Folder 10)
  - Key materials, 1987 (Box 21, Folder 11)
  - Kuvin: Expert report, 1995 July (Box 21, Folder 12)
  - Bragdon Appellate brief - Appendix X 1-221, 1996 (Box 21, Folder 13)
  - Bragdon Appellate brief - Appendix X 222-443, 1996 (Box 21, Folder 14)
  - Bragdon - general, 1995 (Box 22, Folder 1)
  - Expert: Molinari: BK deposition notes/outlines, 1993-1995 (Box 22, Folder 2)
  - Expert Bragdon: Deposition notes, 1994 (Box 22, Folder 3)
  - Ginsburg--Legal history- DC--Cir., 1991-1993 (Box 22, Folder 4)
  - Legal history --Law review articles, 1987-1995 (Box 22, Folder 5)
  - Legal history --Law review articles, 1987-1995 (Box 22, Folder 6)
  - Legal history --Law review articles, 1987-1995 (Box 22, Folder 7)
  - Research, 1995-1997 (Box 23, Folder 1)
  - Research, 1995-1997 (Box 23, Folder 2)
  - Research, 1995-1997 (Box 23, Folder 3)
  - Research, 1997-1998 (Box 23, Folder 4)
  - Research, 1997-1998 (Box 23, Folder 5)
  - Federal Register -- Rules and regulations, 1989 (Box 24, Folder 1)
  - Abbott v. Bragdon: Miscellaneous patients' association TB studies, 1995 (Box 24, Folder 2)
  - Reply brief materials, 1994 (Box 24, Folder 3)
  - Standing Cases, 1994-1997 (Box 24, Folder 4)
  - Abbott v. Bragdon --Miscellaneous articles, 1987-1992 (Box 24, Folder 5)
  - Abbott v. Bragdon --Miscellaneous dental articles, 1989-1994 (Box 24, Folder 6)
  - Abbott v. Bragdon --Miscellaneous dental articles, 1989-1994 (Box 24, Folder 7)
  - Abbott v. Bragdon - Court papers, worksheets, notes, etc., 1997-1999 (Box 24, Folder 8)
  - Abbott v. Bragdon - Court papers, worksheets, notes, etc., 1997-1999 (Box 24, Folder 9)
  - Sidney Abbott miscellaneous: Cooperating agreement, 1995 January (Box 25, Folder 1)
  - Sidney Abbott miscellaneous: Attorney's notes, 1995 (Box 25, Folder 2)
  - Sidney Abbott miscellaneous: Client agreement, 1990 July (Box 25, Folder 3)
  - Sidney Abbott miscellaneous: Doe v. Bragdon settlement agreement, 1995 March (Box 25, Folder 4)
  - Sidney Abbott miscellaneous: Press contacts, Undated (Box 25, Folder 5)
  - Sidney Abbott miscellaneous: News clippings, 1995 May and August (Box 25, Folder 6)
  - Sidney Abbott miscellaneous: Press articles, 1995 July (Box 25, Folder 7)
  - Sidney Abbott miscellaneous: Mark M. Reynolds, D.D.S., C.V., Undated (Box 25, Folder 8)
  - Abbott v. Bragdon - Steven Carter, 1995 June (Box 25, Folder 9)
  - Abbott v. Bragdon miscellaneous: Discovery ideas, 1995 (Box 25, Folder 10)
  - Abbott v. Bragdon miscellaneous: Judge Brody decisions, 1995 March (Box 25, Folder 11)
  - Abbott v. Bragdon miscellaneous:-Health care workers guidelines, 1994 March (Box 25, Folder 12)
  - Abbott v. Bragdon miscellaneous: Michael Glick, D.M.D, 1995 (Box 25, Folder 13)
  - Abbott v. Bragdon miscellaneous: Helene Bednarsh notes, 1995 June (Box 25, Folder 14)
  - Maine -JB info, Undated (Box 25, Folder 15)
  - American Dental Association materials, 1991-1995 (Box 25, Folder 16)
  - Abbott v. Bragdon - Doug Rice jury issues, 1995 August (Box 25, Folder 17)
  - Pleadings: Amended complaint and injunctive relief sought, 1994-1995 (Box 25, Folder 18)
  - Miscellaneous: Patient's Association oral argument, 1995 (Box 25, Folder 19)
  - Sidney Abbott deposition notes, 1995 May (Box 25, Folder 20)
  - Sidney Abbott: Calendar, 1994 -1995 (Box 25, Folder 21)
  - Correspondence, 1994-1995 (Box 26, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence, 1994-1995 (Box 26, Folder 2)
  - Sidney Abbott: Correspondence vol.1, 1994-1995 (Box 26, Folder 3)
  - Sidney Abbott: Correspondence vol.1, 1994-1995 (Box 26, Folder 4)
  - Sidney Abbott: Correspondence vol. 2, 1995-1997 (Box 26, Folder 5)
  - Sidney Abbott: Correspondence, 1995 (Box 26, Folder 6)
  - Abbott v. Bragdon: Correspondence, 1994-1996 (Box 27, Folder 1)
  - Abbott v. Bragdon: Correspondence, 1995-1996 (Box 27, Folder 2)
  - Bragdon: Appeal Correspondence, 1996 (Box 27, Folder 3)
  - Bragdon: Appeal Correspondence, 1997 (Box 27, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence II, 1997-1998 (Box 27, Folder 5)
  - Abbott v. Bragdon: General (7 Floppy disks in this folder), 1994-1999 (Box 27, Folder 6)
  - Abbott v. Bragdon: Bragdon deposition, 1994 October (Box 28, Folder 1)
  - Deposition of Randon Bragdon, MD (original), 1994 November (Box 28, Folder 2)
  - Deposition of Paul H. LaMarche, MD (original), 1994 November (Box 28, Folder 3)
  - Abbott v. Bragdon: Documents also ??? Doe v. Bragdon, 1994 (Box 28, Folder 4)
  - Klein, Bennett H., 1995 (Box 28, Folder 5)
  - Expert Greenspan: Deposition transcript, 1995 July (Box 28, Folder 6)
  - Expert Greenspan: Expert report, 1995 June (Box 28, Folder 7)
  - Expert Greenspan: Documents relied upon in expert report, Undated (Box 29, Folder 1)
  - Expert Greenspan: Documents relied upon in expert report, Undated (Box 29, Folder 2)
  - Expert Greenspan: BK notes/outline, 1995 September (Box 29, Folder 3)
  - Notes from Staff depositions, Undated (Box 29, Folder 4)
  - Staff deposition: Notes and outlines, 1995 August (Box 29, Folder 5)
  - Deposition transcript: Cheryl Bell, 1995 August (Box 29, Folder 6)
  - Deposition transcript: Judith Bragdon, 1995 August (Box 29, Folder 7)
  - Deposition transcript: Kimberly Hayward, 1995 August (Box 29, Folder 8)
  - Deposition transcript: Kristen Long, 1995 August (Box 29, Folder 9)
  - Deposition of Robert Verosloff, M.D., 1995 September (Box 29, Folder 10)
  - Expert Greenspan: Curriculum Vitae, 1994 (Box 29, Folder 11)
  - Bragdon Deposition: Documents produced by Bragdon, 1994 November (Box 30, Folder 1)
  - Guide to documents produced by Bragdon, 1995 May (Box 30, Folder 2)
  - Expert Bragdon: Documents produced, 1995 September (Box 30, Folder 3)
  - Expert Bragdon: Documents produced, 1995 October (Box 30, Folder 4)
  - Expert Bragdon: Inventory(??) of documents produced by Bragdon, Undated (Box 30, Folder 5)
  - Bragdon's documents produced in response to 2nd request for production of documents, 1995 August (Box 30, Folder 6)
  - Expert Bragdon: Deposition signature and errata pages, 1995 July (Box 30, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence and blank health forms, 1995 June (Box 30, Folder 8)
  - Clippings (1 of 2), 1986-1995 (Box 30, Folder 9)
  - Clippings (2 of 2), 1986-1995 (Box 30, Folder 10)
  - Bragdon deposition transcript, 1995 June (Box 31, Folder 1)
  - Documents reviewed by Randon Bragdon Table of contents 1-14, Undated (Box 31, Folder 2)
  - Documents reviewed by Randon Bragdon Table of contents 15-47, Undated (Box 31, Folder 3)
  - Affidavit of John A. Molinari, PH.D, 1995 September (Box 31, Folder 4)
  - Documents produced by John A. Molinari Table of contents 1-10, 1995 August (Box 31, Folder 5)
  - Documents produced by John A. Molinari Table of contents 11-19, 1995 August (Box 31, Folder 6)
  - Expert Marianos: Curriculum vitae, Undated (Box 32, Folder 1)
  - Deposition of Donald Marianos, D.D.S. Pages 1-103, 1995 August (Box 32, Folder 2)
  - Deposition of Donald Marianos, D.D.S. Pages 104-206, 1995 August (Box 32, Folder 3)
  - Expert Marianos: Deposition exhibits, 1995 August (Box 32, Folder 4)
  - Expert Marianos: Documents relied upon in expert report, 1995 August (Box 32, Folder 5)
  - Expert Marianos: Expert report, 1995 June (Box 32, Folder 6)
  - Morvant affidavits, 1995 January (Box 32, Folder 7)
  - Abbott, Sidnet--Plaintiff Appellate Brief, 1995 (Box 32, Folder 8)
  - Memorandum of law in opposition to plaintiff's motion for summmary judgment, Undated (Box 32, Folder 9)
  - Second declaration of Sanford F. Kuvin, 1995 October (Box 32, Folder 10)
  - Correspondence: Remand fromn the Supreme Court, 1998-1999 (Box 32, Folder 11)
  - Gilbert: Defandant's motion for summary judgment, 1995 September (Box 32, Folder 12)
  - McCarthy: Defendant's motion for summary judgment under the ADA ….., 1995 September 19 (Box 32, Folder 13)
  - McCarthy: Defendant's motion for summary judgment under the ADA ….., 1995 September 20 (Box 32, Folder 14)
  - Defendant's rule 19 statement of undisputed material facts, 1995 October (Box 32, Folder 15)
  - Bradgon: Defendant's memo in opposition to Plaintiff's summary judgment motion, 1995 October (Box 32, Folder 16)
  - Defendant's memo in reply to plaintiff's U.S. and Maine Human Rights Commission…, 1995 October (Box 33, Folder 1)
  - McCarthy: List of citations from each deposition, 1995 September (Box 33, Folder 2)
  - Second Affidavit of Randon, Bragdon, D.M.D., 1995 October (Box 33, Folder 3)
  - Trial: USSC rules/practice, Undated (Box 33, Folder 4)
  - Attorney notes, 1992 December (Box 33, Folder 5)
  - Amicus brief materials, 1997 December (Box 33, Folder 6)
  - Amicus notes, 1997 December (Box 33, Folder 7)
  - Current Amicus brief, 1996 July (Box 33, Folder 8)
  - Motion to supplement record, 1995 October (Box 33, Folder 9)
  - Bragdon media comments, Undated (Box 33, Folder 10)
  - Supreme court rules, Undated (Box 33, Folder 11)
  - Abbott v. Bragdon: Preti, Flaherty, Beliveau and Pachios, 1995 August (Box 33, Folder 12)
  - Abbott v. Bragdon: Down East Community Hospital, 1995 August (Box 33, Folder 13)
  - Abbott v. Bragdon: Down East Community Hospital Deposition Trans: David Kennedy, 1995 September (Box 33, Folder 14)
  - Documents from Down East Community Hospital, 1994-1995 (Box 33, Folder 15)
  - McCarthy: Appendix of cases regarding HIV transmission in the health…, 1995-1996 (Box 33, Folder 16)
  - Bragdon misc. The Impact Fund, 1994-1995 (Box 33, Folder 17)
  - The Impact Fund summary sheet, Undated (Box 33, Folder 18)
  - The Impact Fund background of organization and Att., Undated (Box 33, Folder 19)
  - Black subject notebook labeled Notes on oral arguments, Undated (Box 33, Folder 20)
  - First Circuit Remand binder, 1990-1998 (Box 34, Folder 1)
  - Argument forms and info., 1998 January (Box 34, Folder 2)
  - BK- Pending Bragdon notes, 1994 July (Box 34, Folder 3)
  - Bragdon first circuit remand: Pleadings - temporary file, 1998 December (Box 34, Folder 4)
  - Penn State University, 1998 August (Box 34, Folder 5)
  - Hew Regs., 1997 May (Box 34, Folder 6)
  - First circuit rules, Undated (Box 34, Folder 7)
  - Outlines/notes/feedback, 1998 Januarly (Box 34, Folder 8)
  - Outlines/notes/feedback, 1998 Januarly (Box 34, Folder 9)
  - Outlines/notes/feedback, 1998 Januarly (Box 34, Folder 10)
  - Red binder labeled " Bragdon v. Abbott notes", Undated (Box 35, Folder 1)
  - Blue binder with notes, Undated (Box 35, Folder 2)
  - Bragdon summary judgment: Plaintiff's objection to def. motion for summary judgment, 1995 December (Box 35, Folder 3)
  - Bragdon summary judgment: Supplemental affidavit of John A. Molinari, PH.D, 1995 October (Box 35, Folder 4)
  - Bragdon summary judgment: Supplemental affidavit of Donald E. Craven, M.D., 1995 October (Box 35, Folder 5)
  - Bragdon summary judgment: Plaintiff's reply to def. opposition to plaintiff's motion…, 1995 October (Box 35, Folder 6)
  - Bragdon summary judgment: Def. rule 60 motion for relief from order and Inc. memo, 1996 March (Box 35, Folder 7)
  - Bragdon summary judgment: Def. rule 19 statement of undisputed material facts, 1995 September (Box 35, Folder 8)
  - United States Motion and memorandum for Summary judgment…, 1995 September (Box 35, Folder 9)
  - Affidavit of Bernard Benecke, 1995 September (Box 35, Folder 10)
  - Affidavit of John A. Molinari, PH.D, 1995 September (Box 36, Folder 1)
  - Affidavit of John A. Molinari, PH.D, 1995 September (Box 36, Folder 2)
  - Plaintiff Sidney Abbott's record appendix in support of motion for summary judgment, 1995 (Box 36, Folder 3)
  - Plaintiff Sidney Abbott's record appendix in support of motion for summary judgment, 1995 (Box 36, Folder 4)
  - Expert Craven: Expert report, Undated (Box 36, Folder 5)
  - Craven documents produced to McCarthy, 1995 June (Box 36, Folder 6)
  - Expert Craven: Deposition exhibits, 1995 July (Box 36, Folder 7)
  - Expert Craven: Deposition transcription, 1995 July (Box 36, Folder 8)
  - Affidavit of Donald E. Craven, M.D., 1995 September (Box 36, Folder 9)
  - Affidavit of Donald E. Craven, M.D., 1995 September (Box 37, Folder 1)
  - Craven: BK deposition notes/outlines (Box 37, Folder 2)
  - Craven Curriculum Vitae (Box 37, Folder 3)
  - AIDS: Legal Klein/Glad - Articles, 1987-1991 (Box 37, Folder 4)
  - AIDS: Legal Klein/Glad, 1987-1995 (Box 37, Folder 5)
  - AIDS: Legal Klein/Glad, 1995 September (Box 37, Folder 6)
  - AIDS: Legal Klein/Glad, 1984-1995 (Box 37, Folder 7)
  - Clippings, 1993-1995 (Box 38, Folder 1)
  - CDC Guidelines for isolation precautions in hospitals, Undated (Box 38, Folder 2)
  - Expert Bragdon: Documents produced, 1995 September 18 (Box 38, Folder 3)
  - Expert Bragdon: Documents produced, 1995 September 26 (Box 38, Folder 4)
  - Expert Bragdon: Documents produced, 1995 October (Box 38, Folder 5)
  - CDC tuberculosis guidelines, 1995 Sepember (Box 38, Folder 6)
  - Lewis article, 1995 September (Box 38, Folder 7)
  - Patient's Association oral arguments, 1995 September (Box 38, Folder 8)
  - Molinari: Tuberculosis dental outbreak, 1995 July (Box 38, Folder 9)
  - Molinari: Risk data produced, 1989 November (Box 38, Folder 10)